max4u.com 2012-06-17

# 

What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card
information or social security number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your
consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used? to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
How do we protect your information?
Although no system is perfectly secure, we implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order
or access your personal information. Despite these precautions, Max cannot represent or warrant, and by using this website you agree that Max bears no liability
for, any loss, disclosure or theft of personal information submitted to this website or any misuse of that information by any third party.
Do we use cookies?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow). Cookies enable
sites or service providers? systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in
operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your
information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others? rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit (I) our Max4u Website User Agreement (located at http://mxl.myvoffice.com/pdf/en/max4u_user_agreement_en.pdf ) and (ii) our Policies &
Procedures (located at http://mxl.myvoffice.com/pdf/en/policies_procedures_en_US.pdf ) establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability
governing the use of our website.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
http://www.max.com/contactus.php
7090 S. Union Park Ave. Suite 500
Midvale, Utah 84047
U.S.
support@maxgxl.com
801-316-6380
